coupondropdown.com 2016-02-09

# CouponDropDown | Privacy Policy

_Last updated: April 1, 2015_

Thank you for using our browser extension (the "Plugin"). The Plugin is owned and licensed to you by Engaging Apps ("we", "us" or "our"). Downloading and installing the Plugin will result in the display of various types of advertising, which is how we are able to make the Plugin available to you for free. As you use the Plugin, we want you to be clear how we're collecting and using your information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected through the Plugin; however, it does not apply to information collected from our employees, contractors or vendors. Nor does it apply to the information practices of any software or applications downloaded or marketed by third parties, along with the Plugin. Specifically, our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it
  * How we use that information
  * The choices we offer regarding your privacy

We've tried to keep it as simple as possible, but if you're not familiar with terms like cookies, unique identifiers and in-text advertising, then read about these key terms first. Your privacy matters to us, so if you have any questions please contact us. 

Because of the way our Plugin works, certain information may be collected by it but not be accessible to us (or may be accessible only to our service providers who help us power the Plugin). Certain information may be stored by the Plugin and intermittently accessible to us when the Plugin communicates with our systems. For the sake of simplicity, this Privacy Policy covers all information collected by the Plugin and treats it as information to which either our service providers or we may have access, even though in many cases such access may be extremely limited.

1\. **_Advertising Features of the Plugin_**

As mentioned above, the Plugin is supported by advertising, and when you download and install the Plugin you will see various types of advertisements displayed through your browser as you visit locations on the Internet. You should familiarize yourself with these types of advertising, which are features of the Plugin and are listed below.

The Plugin displays several types of advertising, including but not limited to: (1) sponsored links, (2) traditional display advertisements, such as banner ads, pop-up ads and interstitial ads, (3) coupons, (4) video targeted ads (which may be displayed on a webpage, through our own player, or in another window when you view video content on the internet, such as before or after that video content plays), and (5) offers to download and install other applications. The sponsored links may sometimes appear as in-text advertising (ads displayed by converting a particular word(s) into a hyperlink). Sponsored links may also be displayed in response to keyword searches you enter through Google, Bing and other search engines.

2\. **_Personal Information_**

We do NOT knowingly collect personal information through the Plugin. However, it is possible that, in very limited and rare circumstances, personal information could be collected incidentally and without our knowledge (for example, the Plugin collects the URLs of the websites you visit and in certain cases collects the search terms you enter into a search engine, and so if a URL you visit or search term you enter includes the name of an individual, this name would be collected by us).

3\. **_What Information Do We Collect?_**

When the Plugin communicates with our servers, we collect various types of non-personally identifying information. Specifically, we collect web log information which may allow us to determine in which state, city and country you are located (but not your precise geographic location). Web log information also includes information about your browser and device, like the developer and version of your operating system and web browser and your IP address. We also collect information about the Plugin, such as its type and version, what date it was installed, whether it was active on a particular day, or how it was originally distributed to you.

As part of the Plugin’s operations and while the Plugin is installed, we also collect the domain name and URL of the websites you visit (or try to visit, if it is an error) along with other website information, which may help us to determine (among other things) whether we should show an ad. When the search features of the Plugin are enabled and you perform a search, the search terms you enter are also collected, along with the web log information described above.

When the Plugin displays in-text advertising, the technical process we use involves the temporary collection of portions of content on the web page you are visiting. However, in order to avoid collecting your personal information, we take precautions to avoid collecting certain information (e.g., data from form fields) where such information might be entered or displayed. In any case, when we collect web page content in connection with our advertising, we do not use it to find out personal information about you.

4\. **_Cookies and Automatic Information Gathering Technologies._**

We use beacons and other automatic information gathering technologies to collect web log and technical information and, in combination with cookies, store your preferences and other information on your computer or other device. Cookies can store the actual information (e.g. the city, state, or country you are located in) or a unique, pseudonymous identifier that allows us to associate such information with you.

When we use the term “cookies” in this Privacy Policy, we’re referring to the traditional web browser cookie and to newer methods of storing information on your computer, such as “flash cookies,” local browser storage, and storage the web browser makes available to the Plugin. The cookies used by us, our service providers or our advertising partners may store or may be associated with any of the information we collect, including your IP address, the last URL you visited, other technical or generic information such as (but not limited to) the date and time you first used the Plugin, your city, state and country, whether you have clicked on a particular link before, and your decision to opt out of receiving certain types of advertising. We do not use, or allow others to use, cookies (or other automatic information gathering technologies) to collect or store personal information. 

Cookies can be prevented by activating the facility that is available in most web browsers that enables the user to deny or accept cookies. Recognize, however, that if you prevent cookies, the may not function properly. In addition, as explained in more detail in Paragraph 8 below, the decision to opt-out of receiving behavioral advertisements involves the placement of an “opt-out” cookie on your computer; if you disable all cookies, you will likely disable the “opt-out” cookie as well. You should also be aware that flash cookies are more difficult to disable than traditional cookies, and require a user to take affirmative steps to uninstall. Also, some storage needed by the Plugin to operate cannot be disabled without removing the Plugin entirely. 

The cookies that we set may or may not expire, and “flash” cookies typically do not automatically expire (and often need to be removed by the user). We retain the web log and browser history data and aggregate data and reports for our records and to improve our product and services.

5\. **_How Do We Use the Information We Collect?_**

We use the data we collect, including the domain name and URL, to determine which types of advertising to display and which particular ads to show you; to deliver the ads and manage the ad delivery process (including limiting the frequency with which ads can be displayed and honoring your opt-out choices); and to determine compensation under our arrangements with advertising partners and other companies. For example, some websites you visit are not eligible for the display of coupons, so URL or domain data may be used to select the proper type of advertising to display. To give another example, we will not deliver advertising when you visit certain websites, and therefore we sometimes use URL or domain data to turn off the display of ads. We often work with other parties to assist us in delivering advertisements or operating the Plugin, and, in those cases, third parties may use data that we (or they) collect, but only in ways consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

As previously discussed, we may also use cookies, and associate those cookies with unique identifiers, in order for us, our service providers, or a third-party marketing company to collect non-personal information. We will not use this information to personally identify you, will not merge the data with your personally identifying information, and will not try to discover your name or other personally identifying information about you using the data. 

We may use this data to make some types of advertisements more relevant to you and to measure the effectiveness of the ads on behalf of our advertisers, or to create data segments and to measure campaign efficacy. In order to accomplish this, we may link some non-personal information we collect to a unique identifier and infer information about your interests. For example, we may infer that a user uniquely identified by code ABC123 who frequently visits websites about cars is interested in buying a car and associate that user with a category of people interested in buying cars. 

To assist our advertisers in showing you the most relevant ads, we also may work with third-party data providers who already have collected information about you, such as behavioral data (e.g., enjoys watching professional sports or interested in cars) or demographic data (e.g., age range or gender).

The above process is often referred to as “online behavioral advertising” or “OBA.” You can learn more about online behavioral advertising and opt-out of many companies that engage in it by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices. 

Data associated with a unique identifier will only be used for OBA purposes, for our internal product improvement, or, in certain cases, to determine whether a user has previously downloaded a version of our Plugin. We may take collected data and process it into segments or categories; only those segments or categories (along with a unique identifier) will be shared with advertisers or others (“Profile Data“).

We may also use some of the web log information we collect, including what we refer to as system and zone identifiers, to help us get a better understanding of our overall user base (for example, to determine how many of our users use Internet Explorer, how many are Mac users, etc.) and the web domains they access, as well as how many active users of the Plugin there are on a given date. We may also use this information for other internal purposes, such as to help us diagnose problems, to perform research, reporting and analysis aimed at improving our Plugin and other technologies, to manage our systems, and to evaluate the performance of our relationships with other companies.

We are always looking for ways to improve our products. To that end, we periodically collect and analyze how you interact with our software and the websites you visit, such as interactions with our software features, files downloaded, and advertisements viewed or clicked on. Web log information, including your IP address, may also be collected and stored by our service providers and marketing partners so that they may improve their own products and services.

You should be aware that when you click on ads displayed through the Plugin or submit information to an advertiser or other third-party marketer, that third party may also collect your information for online behavioral advertising. Some of our advertisers may themselves drop cookies used for online behavioral advertising on your computer when you interact with their ads.

6\. **_Disclosure of Your Information_**

We disclose information we collect about you to third parties (including without limitation our corporate affiliates, advertisers, coupon providers and partners who bundle and distribute our Plugin) as reasonably necessary to display our various types of advertising, to track the performance of our relationships with these third parties, and to determine compensation and manage our respective business relationships. We may also share web log information with third-party marketers so that they can target ads to you based on a single domain or search term request, or, as mentioned above, on your overall browsing history. To assist our advertisers in showing you the most relevant ads, service providers, our third-party marketers, or we may share Profile Data with advertisers and other parties who facilitate the delivery of advertisements. Finally, we disclose information to service providers engaged to perform other functions on our behalf (such as providing data storage, hosting, ad serving, content distribution, marketing of our Plugin and other products, auditing, and web analytics). Since we do not knowingly collect personal information, we do not share it with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.

We may also disclose your information, anonymously aggregated with information about other users of our products and services, to our clients, business partners, merchants, advertisers, investors, potential buyers and other third parties if we deem such disclosure, in our sole discretion, to have sound business reasons or justifications. For example, when a third party bundles our Plugin with its own downloadable application and distributes the bundled applications together, we may share with the third party the total number of installations of the Plugin our systems have recorded.

We may disclose your information to third parties when we believe, in good faith and in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) enforce or apply the end-user license or other terms and conditions for the Plugin, including investigation of any potential violations, (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements or a governmental request, (c) protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users or other third parties, (d) prevent a crime or protect national security, or (e) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

Finally, if we are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, liquidation or receivership of our business, we will provide affected users notice through the www.www.CouponDropDown.com website or the Plugin at least thirty (30) days before your information becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

7\. **_Accessing Your Information; Transparency and Choice_**

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used.

As mentioned above, we do not knowingly collect personal information. Since we do not collect personally identifying information (such as your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or credit card number) (“PII”) we do not maintain a process for an individual to review and/or request changes to his or her PII. However, if you believe that we have inadvertently collected any personal information about you, please contact us and we will try to locate and delete this information. We may ask you to identify yourself and the information requested to be accessed or deleted before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backups), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case, where we provide information access and deletion, we will perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

If you would like to opt out of the Plugin collecting and sharing data for online behavioral advertising purposes, please uninstall the Plugin. The opt-out we provide only stops our own collection of the behavioral data through the Plugin; other websites may still collect your data and advertisers may use that data to show you targeted ads (see http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ for more information). In addition, you can stop all data collection and advertising through the Plugin if you uninstall it by following the instructions here. 

8\. **_Third Party Links, Sites and Applications_**

Please note that the Plugin may provide links to third party sites. For example, when you click on an advertisement displayed through the Plugin, you are taken to a web page which is not owned or controlled by us. Additionally, a feature of the Plugin may offer you a menu of third-party software applications that you may download if you choose to do so. Also, third parties who bundle our Plugin with their own or other third party software applications may collect end-user data through separately installed applications and not through the Plugin. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy policies, practices or the content of websites, web pages, or applications owned by others, and their collection of information from you is not governed by this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of service of those sites and applications when you visit them and before installing any applications so that you understand how they collect, use and share your information.

9\. **_International Users_**

By installing and using the Plugin and providing us with your information, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of the Plugin we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such information may be stored on servers located in the United States. The data protection and privacy laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By installing and using the Plugin, you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States, and you further agree that all transactions relating to the Plugin or our website shall be deemed to have occurred in the United States.

10\. **_Children_**

The Plugin is not intended for users under 18 years of age. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child under the age of 18, we will delete that data from our systems. 

11\. **_Information Security_**

We utilize reasonable information security measures to safeguard your Information. For example, we utilize Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology when data is transmitted over the Internet, and have installed firewalls to help prevent external access into our network. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet and no method of data storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its security.

While we do not seek to collect personal information, when we collect information that is associated with unique identifier, we restrict access to it to our employees, contractors, service providers and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Plugin. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

12\. **_Changes to this Policy_**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not materially reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without notice to you. We will post any privacy policy changes on www.CouponDropDown.com/privacy.php or notify you about them through the Plugin and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a prominent notice (such as an alert through the Plugin). You can always check the "Last Updated" date at the top of our Privacy Policy to see when it was last changed, and we encourage you to check it at www.CouponDropDown.com/privacy.php from time to time. 

13\. **_Questions_**

For inquiries about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.
